=================== WELCOME TO THE BEATROOT® COMMUNITY! ====================
Instructions:

General

Click on an album thumbnail to see the whole album and load the first song of the album
into the player. 
Double-click on a song in the list underneath the player to load into the player.
The song will play automatically.
Click on the download button on the top right corner of the welcome menu to download the
playing song on your computer.
----------------------------------------------------
Rating & comments

Only songs loaded into the player can be rated and commented.
Click on the pen icon next to the rating stars to add a comment to the song loaded in the player.
Click on the stars to add a rating to the same song.
Only premium users can rate and comment songs.
----------------------------------------------------
Playlists

Click on the green plus button next to the Playlist list to create a new playlist.
Right-click on the song loaded on the player to add it to a playlist of your choice.
Select a playlist from the list and click on the red minus button to delete it.
Right-click on the list of songs underneath the playlist list to remove it from the playlist.
----------------------------------------------------
Contacts

Search for a premium or trial user on the search bar on the right of the welcome menu.
Click on the magnifying lens icon to open their user page.
If:
 o you are a premium user;
 o the selected contact is a premium user;
 o the selected contact is not your contact already, and
 o the selected contact does not have any pending contact requests
you will be able to send them a contact request. If they accept, they will be added to your contact list 
underneath the search bar. To remove them, right-click on their name on the list.
If you are a premium user and have a contact request, you will see a little star on the message icon at the 
top right corner. Click on the icon and you will be able to see who sent you the contact request.
You can accept it or decline it. 
----------------------------------------------------
Searching

Search for a song, album or artist on the search bar at the top center of the welcome page.
Select a matching result and click on the magnifying lens icon to load the song/album 
on the player. If you search for an artist, select one of their suggested albums and click on the
magnifying lens to load it.
